Open your eyes, open your mind. We are
the Wings. Sup everyone. Tim5 here with
a very special video. Today we're
looking at episode three of the Wings
Club. The magic is back. Right away, we
are thrown into the episode with the
monster from episode one breaking and
entering into like the Wings's dorm
room. And and I got to be honest, I was
surprised like, okay, continuity, we're
doing this [__] We're actually doing
this. I do wonder how the hell the
monster was able to get into the school
completely unnoticed, though. Like he
goes rumaging through the [__] and
steals Stella's magic ring and immediate
scadaddles. Like where was the security?
I I didn't get that. Bloom and her pack
of fairy [__] return to the room
talking about now that Bloom's a fairy,
it's time for her to awaken her fairy
form and [__] And after going upstairs,
Stella realizes her ring was stolen.
It's here that we learn it's not just a
normal ring, but a special magical
artifact like type [__] and which
magically enhances the magic of who's
whoever's wearing it, which you would
think would be bad at like a fairy
school where they use magic. Wouldn't
this make her better than literally
everybody else in the school, including
her friends? Why don't they speak up? Is
it because Stella is rich and they want
the benefits of being her friend? I I
think so cuz now that I think about it,
everybody in the wings sub seems to not
like her very much. Like now that I
think about it. So they look around the
room and immediately find monster
tracks. And upon closer inspection, it's
not just dirt, but also Ash from a from
a an evil dog place. I I I I don't
remember the name of it. I don't really
care. But it's like some old ruins where
the Trixes live live and [__] Those are
the three evil witch [__] By the
way, if if you've forgotten what they're
called, the they're they're the tricks.
Now, at this point, the plan should be
simple, right? Tell the witch professors
or or or the cops, the specialists that
the trickers stole your [__] and brought
a monster and get their asses like
thrown in jail. But here in Alfa, we
don't do that here. Instead, they just
go to class and act like nothing
happened. Like, I guess. Also, just look
how the walking class. It's like in a
straight line holding the books and
[__] I I just wanted to share this cuz
I thought it was kind of creepy like
like some like some like some cult [__]
But Bloom separates from the gang and
goes to the library. And of course the
first book she grabs she finds a map of
the ruins just by only being in Alfa for
like 3 days. And and oh and okay
[__] I I don't know how what how bad
you say this except she like hears the
voice of like a toddler or some some
baby
huh
it's me
like it's some real horror movie [__]
like Bloom come over here like yeah like
she so she goes towards the voice it's
weird as [__] that's how you know she's
like the w white one in the group
because any of the other fairies would
be get getting out of this [__] And
it's here that we learn about a thing
called the dragon flame. What whatever
the hell that is. I I don't know. I
don't give a [__] So Bloom is like,
"Yo, [__] check out this map of the
ruins." Like, "Oh my god, Bloom, shut
up. Class is about to stop." Oh my god.
Oh my god. Why is he here? Do the girls
not got no other class to go to the
school? Why is there a leprechaun in
this show? What? Why? Why did Why did
the leprechaun appear in two episodes
out of three? We We had to watch a show
about fairies. Is every episode going to
be a St. Patrick's Day special at this
point? Like dead ass. This is bananas.
Like he he brought his stupid small
house to school. Like we're doing show
and tell that he's like I guess a
homeowner or some [__] because in this
economy that's like an accomplishment
few can only dream of. And for class
they're learning transfiguration
transfiguration and [__] That's That's
when you turn things into other things,
right? Yeah. So, he put a lock in his
own little house. Actually, I don't know
who put it there. They didn't really
say, actually, now that I think about
it, what if somebody put the lock on the
door to keep him in, but somehow he
keeps getting out. I don't know. So,
he's staring to turn the lock into
something else so he can be rid of the
chains for good and so he can go inside
his tiny stupid house. And and and they
do it. They turn it into a necklace
which he just takes and starts rocking
and rolling and and we don't know why he
does that. He just does. So they head to
the ruins, right? They decided they're
going to take the fat to to the [__] to
the Trixes. And you know what? I like
where this is going. We're heading into
a gang war up in this [__] The
leprechaun is not coming with us and the
Trixes are outnumbered 5 to three. We're
going to make sure these bullies never
mess with us again. We even get to see
some of Techno's abilities. We found out
she used her technology, magic, or
whatever it is to save a copy of the Mac
map of the ruins. And they found like a
baby, a baby locked in like a cage. We
get a call back and [__] to what they
learned in the stupid little leprechauns
class and the transfiguration and the
revelations that Techno can literally
record events like in real time like
through her eyeballs and that helps her
and the girls remember the spell they
need to cast to break the lock. But plot
was [__] The baby monster we was
actually the the big monster. And also
he's got like an army of baby Yodas from
Star Wars the Mandalorian. But then we
find out this was a setup by the Twixes
because of course it was. So here it is
[__] The battle we've all been
waiting for. The Winxes versus the [__]
the witches. We get this cool
transformation sequence that lasts like
45 seconds only for Aussie to use her
powers to trap them in a big ball of ice
10 seconds later. Not not not Bloom
though. She's always fine. So get this.
The ice makes like actual ice box that
are closing clo slowly closing in to
like kill them. Like yes, this is this
is actually happening me. Like I was
surprised too. It's like no longer kitsu
at this point. The pack of evil lesbians
out are out dead ass evil. Like this
goes beyond bullying at this point. This
is attempted murder. Dead ass. This is
the first moment so foul that guy would
stand up from the toilet cuz you know I
was taking a [__] I was watching weeks
club like while taking a [__] How How
do all these girls expect to go to class
tomorrow? Assuming you you you know they
all make it out alive. Like this is some
traumatic [__] [__] Like somebody
called the cops. Like thankfully Bloom
as we know is a fire fairy. I'm guessing
something to do with the dragon's flame.
What? Whatever the hell I don't know. I
don't give a [__] And [__] So she
awakens your fire form. O open your
mind. Open your eyes. We are the the
wings. Wings. If your hand is holding
mine, we can fly through space and time
and together we'll be sure winners. And
she frees like the girls and they get
out of there. And then they go back to
the school. They run into like the
librarian. I I didn't mention her, but
there's like a librarian and [__] She
She ran into Bloom in It doesn't matter.
But she like gets mad at them for being
after conf but tell them what happened,
[__] Tell the tr Tell tell her the
Trixers tried to murder you. Why aren't
you saying anything? Get those [__]
expelled.
Mr. Electric, send him to the
principal's office and have him
expelled.
Lock up or something. This This is why
the Trixers keep doing what they do cuz
they aren't facing any repercussions.
Techno, you record you recorded the
classroom with your techno powers.
Surely you record the fight against the
Trixes to show them show them what
happened. Like do your job. What are you
doing? And then okay, they do go to the
professors, but all they say is that it
was the Trix's fault that they would
pass curfew. That's it. B [__] that's
all you're going to say? No. No mention
of the monster or the evil baby Yodas
from the Star Wars or the deadly evil
spaxs. Bloom bloom blue. The spacks
and and they have nerf to just go back
to their rooms and have a dance party.
And they order some disgusting ass
pizza. Look. Look at that. That is not
good. That does not look edible. What is
that? What is that? Look, look how weird
it is. I'm losing my mind watching this
[__] Oh. Oh my god. Oh my god. Open
your eyes. Open your mind. We are the
Wings. So, here here is where we finally
learn why the show is called Wings Club.
Bloom has a great idea where she says if
they're called Tricks, then their team
name should be called the Wings Club. I
I still don't get that cuz both both Is
it cuz both end with the letter X? I I
get tricks like the play on the wood
trick or like tricks tricks off for
kids. You know that that that's serial
[__] But why wings? Like winking or is
it cuz they have wings? Like they fly?
Like the others literally ask Bloom what
winks means? Cuz even they don't know
like us. And Bloom is like I don't know.
I don't know [__] Why you asking me?
But you came up with it. Oh, also we
find out that I see Stormmy and Dia
working for Giant F Grindleald. And also
Bloom's magic is like super strong. And
yeah, his called the dragon's flame and
and Johnny Depp's Grinwald wants it.
That's it. So overall, I got to say
pretty good episode. Like I I like how
the witches actually tried to kill the
fairies, even though it was kind of
weird how Bloom and the girls didn't
tell anybody after what's going to
happen. What's going to happen when they
go to the school tomorrow? Are they just
going to act like nothing happened? Cuz
like that was attempted murder. Like,
can somebody go to the police about this
[__] Not even for your own protection,
but like for the protection of the other
students at the school. This school
sucks. The teachers like I I don't like
the librarian, [__] I don't like
anyone at this school. They They're all
bad. I think I'll give it a four out of
10, though, cuz again, I like AI,
Stormmy, and Darcy, and how they they
give no shits. They they get [__] done
and they're bad [__] Even if
even if they technically could be dealt
with fast if somebody just told told a
parent or guardian about them that's and
what's going on at school. Actually, you
know what? No, I I'm giving this episode
a 2 out of 10 cuz I I literally just
remember the little leprechaun man was
in the episode and he takes two boys off
from the overall score. So yeah, I I I
hope I don't see him again for the rest
of the show or his creepy little house.
I want somebody to lock him in. That
would be that would be kind of funny. If
you like what I do, consider supporting
me on Patreon. I I I have things that
you can go look at over there.
Life is harder than I like to think, but
it's easy when you're by my side. No
point in calling. You just have to see
the fundamentals of our life tonight.
Cuz I've been looking at a photograph of
you. And I've been thinking about all
the ways you move. This isolation got me
feeling like a moon, my love.
When I wake up, I feel empty, not beside
you. My whole life been searching just
to find you. is for it. Hasn't got the
right to
killing time. We got nowhere to be.
You're sending messages I can't ignore.
contemplating coming close to me. I'm
bored at home. Can't leave the house no
more. But I've been looking at a
photograph of you and I've been thinking
of all the ways you this isolation got
me feeling like you're my love.
And when I wake up, I feel empty now
beside you. My whole life been searching
just to find you. is crossing. It hasn't
got the right to
so far.
You know, I feel beside you. My whole
life is searching just to find you.
It hasn't got the right to
so far.